The Azure of Celestia Game Music (Asset Vol.10)
(Ver1.01)

Thank you for purchasing!

A collection of music materials depicting the world of a magnificent fantasy adventure JRPG!

This music material is created with the motif of a magnificent fantasy adventure JRPG.
A warm and relaxing music with a slightly ethnic feel.
Orchestra style music that creates a high-quality feeling of power and thrill that can be used in cinema scenes and fight themes.
Inspiring piano, violin, vocal songs that produce emotional and sensual plot scenes and climaxes.

By adopting this material song as the background music of your work that creates a fantastic different world, such as the theme of stars and life, you will be able to further bring out the charm of the story.

The final track vocal song "Sea La" is written by Yheri Kang (ELLEY), who continues to be active as a world-class singer-songwriter singing in three languages.

In addition, this work was created by the developer who developed the action game "Sword Master Story", which made it into the top 10 at the Google Play Indie Games Festival 2020 in South Korea and has exceeded 10 million downloads in total in 150 countries around the world. Under the supervision, from the perspective of the game developer, we are constantly giving multifaceted feedback on the usability of the music, and it has been improved to a more sophisticated music.
We hope that the ease of use as a material will make it possible to create games with a high degree of player satisfaction, making daily creation more enjoyable.

In this package you'll find totally 17 music tracks. 
There are 1 vocal track, 16 instrumental tracks.
All of the wav tracks are available as high quality 16 bit, and high quality re-mastered for using in games.
And, this pack includes ogg vorbis seamless loop and mpeg-4 aac version of each music track.


Before you use, Please confirm you agree to our terms and conditions for use. 
https://airyluvs.com/policies/terms-of-service


-------Version Released

Ver1.03
Jul 02, 2021 Fixed #04, #06 ogg looping point. Added BPM information and #15 lyrics in readme.txt

Ver1.01
Jun 01, 2021 Fixed #07 ogg looping point


May 31, 2021 First release


------

Track list

01. The Azure of Celestia (2:48) bpm156
02. Whispering Fate (5:32) bpm72
03. Sleeping Maneuver (2:44) bpm56
04. The Imperial City, Evernauts (3:15) bpm159
05. Bottakuri Pedra (1:39) bpm121
06. A Long Journey (4:02) bpm90
07. Road to the Skyland (2:57) bpm137
08. Eyes On Darkness II (3:07) bpm137
09. Passed Away (2:19) bpm97
10. Slash (2:31) bpm116
11. Quietness (2:30) bpm free
12. Magatsuhinokami (2:24) bpm152
13. Alcantarea (2:11) bpm free
14. Lethaldose (2:59) bpm128
15. Sea La.. (3:13) bpm72
16. Niji no zannei (2:40) bpm free
17. Sea La..(Instrumental) (3:13) bpm72



Produced by ISAo
SOUND AIRYLUVS

►YouTube Channel 
https://www.youtube.com/c/ISAoGameMusic

►Website
https://airyluvs.com/

►twitter
https://twitter.com/airyluvs_eng

►twitter(JP)
https://twitter.com/airyluvs


:Credits:

Composer
Isao Yamaguchi

Character Illustration
Zorra

Track Supervisor
CodeCAT

Vocal & Lyrics (Tr.15)
姜藝利（ELLEY)

Music Produced by SOUND AIRYLUVS




--------

# 15 Sea La..  Lyrics by 姜藝利（ELLEY)

Farewell, dear my little one Come kiss me for last time
Whenever you miss me much Look up the glowing stars
You don’t know meaning of say goodbye, so 
How can I leave you alone?
No matter every hope and light are vanishing 
Feel so hard to breathe, don’t try to give up 
Remember what stars saying
No matter how far I’ll be there for you 
Far beyond the horizon I will sing
Hear the ocean sings 
Sea La..

It’s okay, my dear, you’re not alone 
Every piece of love for you is now here 
How priceless you, you are
Whatever you decide I’m on your side 
Always pray for you to be happy Hear the ocean sings
Sea La..


--------




*If you want to order custom music for your project, please contact me.
isao@airyluvs.com

Thanks.
May 31, 2021
